okay real quick periscope chase this is
a shout-out to you you asked for a
scoping Thursday I'm gonna show you guys
let's go be Thursday so what we're
discussing today let me just put my
laptop away here is right here for sale
on shop comma dot ai
not to be confused with my Thai iced tea
which is not for sale I'm chopped I copy
that I our periscope chase did it you
did it you yes okay
we're showing off is the comma snakes so
much of new pictures of them all look
how nice oh you did a great job with
these oh they look great look at that
new look so they no longer have that
terrible looking tape I do like the fort
we haven't worked that much on the Ford
yet we are here talking about the comma
space so there's a common space and here
I have one right here so your comes
means won't have this terribly ugly tape
this is connected here to a comedy bug a
nakama panda you guys all know these
products comedy bug so just to show you
all look at the new URL that's not to be
you I listen to you I don't know it's
not yeah I'll just show you what you can
do with your comma space so like I've
said that Ethernet is connected let me
just go in here and press all the
buttons I need to bring up a new
terminal and you just tie SS h chase
asked me to show off the space on on on
periscope so gonna show off the snakes
so I can just SSH so this this Ethernet
cable here
it's just connected right to my oh yeah
great of an artist thing okay we'll give
you a sneak preview of the UI as well
but first so right here you can see that
I'm SS aged into my eon right here Oh to
see the new UI you ever seen it yeah
wait you want to just bring it up on a
if you just put the switch on Andrews is
that gonna work and you can see right
here I'm in your manager you just flip
the switch on that know what the switch
on the debug yeah
flip the switch when move okay so we
have way too much of the company you're
trying to huh I'm going to get work here
are the carefully reverse-engineered
state machines from the Toyota ECU oh
look there's some information about the
UI down in that corner now I know what
I'm bringing you guys agree you got into
the stockroom to look at all of the
spaces I think they're in this bin right
here look at these comma spaces
beautiful fresh maze each and every one
of them look at that stage what else do
we have up here oh we have comma powers
Oh Colin powers no way to comma powers
are good but this is a debug born
check out the debug boards it's simply
amazing check out our new red pause we
got a tub full of red pause over here we
got pandas in little boxes oh how nice
of these boxes you I I got guys and
let's see if I can finally come up this
look it's a box of unfinished giraffes
look at Jeff's dress you know what these
are the grant pandas aren't in stock yet
but this is a huge box full of antennas
and we just ordered a thousand more else
so we have a thousand more antennas
coming up there's some eons in
production right there check out those
zeroes are pretty nice alright as a new
UI still loading oh it's low yeah
what do you mean we need to market it
well I'm not sure they need to mock
daily you just need to flip the switch
is there any version to master yes
oh-hoo blue wire doesn't want to hold
the scobie's well I pull master yeah
I'm not turning with moanitors I don't
do that so actually you can see
that SSH tin with my comma space so very
useful by a commis maze today and if you
buy panda all pandas shipping now come
in the cutest little boxes you've ever
seen there's a panda box right here
check it out comma dot AI slash setup
you can go to that one so let's go to
that website setup guidance get started
with your new comma AI product to
improve your driving experience today
Panda download the shipper dash cam app
plug panda into your car OVD poi finish
pairing with your shipper app how do you
guys like the new pairing thing where's
it taking forever to download
Josh could you include with on that
marketing what you know I took the what
why what needs improving you don't like
the Box box is nice websites nice yeah
so at least I've been here maybe maybe
the new I works the new UI is nice
that's worth waiting for
we could show we could shown that boy
that's a nice boy yeah yeah look at the
cameras out watch it Steve
oh it's loading Oh guys it's got a it's
got to compile to MPC which takes
forever
what can we show for in the mean get
your midnight black er today this is the
nicest Eon money can buy it's only eight
hundred and twenty nine dollars it comes
with a midnight black heatsink this is a
midnight black built-in compute
unit we've stopped using the p-word
[Laughter]
that's not the P word you don't want
these panels built alright so guys this
is a live demo I really have no idea of
this game yeah check out master I did ok
let's flip the switch right here on my
comedy bug board
yo that's that's pretty nice but I think
that's Oh does it go away would I do
that
yes oh man this is nice stuff people how
to switch two ways oh you just press
this convenient button and then you
press ways and now you're in waves
switch to Spotify very convenient press
here switch back to open pilot oh look
though the lane really goes away when
there's no way no that's nice that's
nice this lights up I think when you're
engaged or something wasteful skiing -
no actually no we don't need the
sidewalk so you can go back to a full
screen mode
oh the pilot only gets full screen what
we call this is using hidden api's for
only our products I think Microsoft
gonna sue for that but clearly it's ok
now look at Apple all right guys open
this let's open this Amazon Prime
together as a parting gift
tear out perforation
to open I really don't know what's in
here those are the fan that I lost my
show do we improve the fan policy no
probably not as much as much well we
would open the Amazon Prime but
unfortunately we're out of time
no bonus mean today yeah so enjoy a new
UI and go shop accommodate a I make sure
to by Thomas phases come space alright
alright